I wouldn't be this
technology if I didn't
believe that the good
outweighed the and that
we could the bad
That's why I about
the bad so that
we could How do
you think we mitigate
it Does that mean
things like taxation Yeah
well let me just
get to what I
think kind the situation
is I think exactly
what you said I
think we could have
this very unusual combination
of very fast GDP
growth and high unemployment
or at least underemployment
or low wage jobs
a lot of low
wage jobs high inequality
I don't think that's
a macro correct me
if I'm wrong don't
think that's a macroeconomic
combination we've ever seen
before You think of
fast growth you're like
well okay maybe there's
inflation But you're not
gonna have high unemployment
when there's fast growth
I think this technology
is a different because
it's extreme in the
way it's gonna generate
value But also because
it's moving up the
cognitive waterline there's gonna
be a whole class
of people who are
think across a of
going to have a
hard time coping And
that's really a problem
we need to